//array of questions
const questions = [
  {
    question: "Amount of players that can be played on the field in soccer?",
    answers: {
      a: "7",
      b: "11",
      c: "2",
      d: "8",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "Amount of players that can be played on court in basketball",
    answers: {
      a: "5",
      b: "3",
      c: "4",
      d: "12",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Amount of players that can be played in tennis?",
    answers: {
      a: "2",
      b: "4",
      c: "neither",
      d: "both",
    },
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "Amount of players that can be played on the field in baseball?",
    answers: {
      a: "10",
      b: "11",
      c: "18",
      d: "9",
    },
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "Amount of players that can be played in volleyball?",
    answers: {
      a: "5",
      b: "6",
      c: "7",
      d: "8",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "Amount of players that can be played on the field in football?",
    answers: {
      a: "8",
      b: "11",
      c: "10",
      d: "9",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Amount of players that can be played on the field in ice hockey?",
    answers: {
      a: "6",
      b: "5",
      c: "8",
      d: "9",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Amount of players that can be played in badminton?",
    answers: {
      a: "4",
      b: "2",
      c: "neither",
      d: "both",
    },
    correctAnswer: "d",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Amount of players that can be played on the field in field hockey?",
    answers: {
      a: "11",
      b: "10",
      c: "13",
      d: "9",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Amount of players that can be played on the field in rugby?",
    answers: {
      a: "16",
      b: "15",
      c: "19",
      d: "18",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
  },
];
export { questions };
